Jennifer Debono

(H) 519-854-6714 | jennifer.debono79@gmail.com | 451 Berkshire Dr, London, ON N6J 3R5

SUMMARY

Tech-savvy and accurate GIS Technician bringing 7+ years of experience in municipal planning settings. Manages diverse projects, studies, and inquiries both independently and with a multidisciplinary team to provide results within tight deadlines. Conscientious, detail-oriented; easily follows relevant standards and procedures.

SKILLS

- Strong technical skills (e.g. MS Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Access, document management software and use of ESRI and AutoCAD)
- Experience preparing graphic materials (ie. Sketch Up, Adobe Illustrator, Photoshop)
- Strong multi-tasking, time management, analytical and organization skills
- Adaptable, driven, and a confidant decision maker
- Excellent interpersonal skills

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

Diploma - GIS & Urban Planning Fanshawe College President's List

Honours B.A – Anthropology University of Western Ontario Dean's Honour List 2010 London, ON

2007 London, ON

EXPERIENCE

Planning Technician, COUNTY OF MIDDLESEX, 2012-2019 London, ON

- Preparation of planning reports, notices, and mapping
- Consolidation of planning documents to facilitate information distribution for staff and public use
- Organization of planning files, data bases and technical processes
- Maintained key data sets for internal and external distribution
- Inspected sites to assess validity and feasibility of submitted development plans
- Illustrated results of planning studies with reports, charts, and graphs
- Liaised between planning teams, outside departments and the public
- Processed planning applications, verifying information against established standards

Jennifer Debono

(H) 519-854-6714 | jennifer.debono79@gmail.com | 451 Berkshire Dr, London, ON N6J 3R5

Planning Technician & Graphic Design, COMMUNITY PLANNERS INC, 2010-2012 London, ON

- Database management
- Prepared presentation materials and summaries for public meetings
- Reviewed & prepared Planning Act applications
- Updated and consolidated zoning by-law/official plan documents
- Provided research and analysis for various planning issues and projects
- Performed general office administration tasks including basic IT problem solving, and customer service
- Illustrated results of planning projects with reports, charts, and graphs

Student Geomatics Technician - Coop, MINISTRY OF TRANSPORTATION, 2009 London, ON

- Digitized ownership parcels for the Southwestern Ontario Region
- Maintained the parcel & title record database
- Prepared reference maps
- Assisted with by-law and legislation research

Supervisor – Tim Hortons, 2008-2010 London, ON

Field Technician – Timmins-Martelle Heritage Consultants, 2005 London, ON

CERTIFICATIONS

Member, Canadian Association for Certified Planning Technicians (CACPT) Member, URISA Ontario

Jennifer Debono

(H) 519-854-6714 | jennifer.debono79@gmail.com | 451 Berkshire Dr, London, ON N6J 3R5

REFERENCES

Russel Schnurr
Program Co-Ordinator; GIS & Urban Planning
School of Art & Design
Fanshawe College
1001 Fanshawe College Boulevard
London, ON N5Y 5R6
P: 519-452-4430 x.4322
E-mail: rschnurr@fanshawec.ca

Ben Puzanov, MCIP, RPP Manager, Planning & Development Services

The County of Lambton 789 Broadway Street, Box 3000 Wyoming, ON NON 1T0 P: 519 845-0801 x 5342

E-mail: Ben.Puzanov@county-lambton.on.ca

Dan Smith
Senior Planner
Monteith Brown Planning Consultants
610 Princess Avenue
London, Ontario N6B 2B9
P: 519-686-1300 x.243

E-mail: dsmith@mbpc.ca